I never dreamed before
I'm gonna knock the door
into the world of perfect free
(You ain't no lonely!)
You're gonna say I'm lying
I'm gonna get the chance
I thought a chance is far from me
(You ain't no lonely!)
I was made to hit in America
(I was made to hit in America)
You are the sun, you are the star
(To me, forever)
I was made to hit in America
(I was made to hit in America)
Huh?
Did you get the shell?
You?
Just answer my question.
It'll be all good.
All the white dudes will be sad
if Eddy Lee's dead, right?
For me, I don't give a fuck!
Who told you to do this?
Hey! Hey!
I'm asking you!
Where the fuck is this thing you stole?
Say what?
Whoa Eddy! Are you all right?
Yeah. He took off right when
the security guys came in.
I see. You are still lucky.
I knew it! He found out everything.
Can't be. How could he find out?
Ray, the movie's done.
Our tour movie, that Jim directed.
Yeah?
Yeah, they've been previewing it
a couple of times last week...
What?
Yeah, I told Jim to cut out
the scene of me playing, "Lucille."
You know, he's an artist.
Well...
Yeah, it was the uh...
It was the scene of Koyuki.
You know, singing really, really good.
"Live 16 'Indies'"
I'll come again!
What's with that kid?
He comes in everyday, smiling.
Gives me the creeps.
I hear if you keep staring at a Telecaster,
it helps you endure even hard labor.
Oh...
But...
He'd better make up his mind
or it'll be sold.
Hey! Hey!
Where're the spring rolls?!
Oh sorry!
Hey Tanaka! The dumplings are overdone.
I just got a complaint.
-I'm sorry!
-Hey, spring rolls!
Right!
Hey Tanaka!
You didn't ladle the soup carefully!
The same customer is complaining!
I'm sorry.
Strange...I'm doing it properly.
My goodness!
-How many times must I complain
before you get things right?!
-I'm so sorry.
-How can I pay for this?
-Huh? It's Saito-san...
I thought they'd give me a free meal.
-What a stingy shop.
-You're the stingy one!
I'm counting on you for Tuesday.
I have lots of deliveries.
I guess I'll go to the bathhouse.
Ouch!
Maybe I'll go meet that girl who works
at the doughnut shop next door.
Hey! Quit loafing and get back to work!
Oh, sorry!
He's so cool!
Well, too bad! Yoshito belongs to me!
No way! Yoshito's mine!
-Hey!
-Excuse me!
"Yoshito Morozumi"
Is this guy popular?
Are you serious? You don't
watch TV on Mondays at 8?
It's a sad drama about
a short-distance runner.
I sooo love it!
Yoshito plays a young guy in
a wheelchair. And he's awesome.
Oh...
Good, we had a good crowd tonight.
I'm totally beat!
-You'll get paid nicely tonight.
-Really?
Hey Tanaka-kun!
There's a female customer
named Minami asking for you.
Huh? Maho?
She's quite cute.
Your girlfriend?
No...nothing like that.
Hi!
Hey, doesn't that boy look familiar?
Huh?
-He's the one in the drama.
-A-And that water commercial!
-Ryusuke told me you worked here.
-Oh...
You sure are working hard.
Nah...Not really.
Oh yeah, let me introduce you...
This is one of my classmates, Yoshito.
We met once in Mi-chan's shop.
You're on TV, right? That's awesome.
Hey Maho...this guy looks so dirty.
You sure the food here is okay?
-Koyuki, are you free on Monday?
-Why?
It's Christine's birthday party.
I wondered if you could come.
Christine?
What?
I thought we were gonna have this party
only with friends from school.
Why not? It's always more fun
with more people.
What do you mean?
We already have enough people.
Why are you so unhappy about it?
-Wow! They're bilingual!
-And she's so pretty.
They were eating the 5000-yen course.
Hope they have money.
And I can't even speak English.
Hey kid!
Quit daydreaming!
I'm sorry!
No, thank you so much! Good-bye!
Every label turned us down?
Our self-produced CD is a total disaster.
We worked so hard on it.
Ran's influence was worse than I expected.
No one would come right out and say it,
but I could feel Ran's influence.
Can we break through it? With our power?
Ran...
Lift up your heavy ass, now
If you take off that stiff head
You'll feel totally loose
This crazy, crazy world
-Well...the sound is still amateur...
-You just have to Stage Dive or Die
-but I do feel some good vibes from it
-Mind blower, a shower of sweat
even with a name like Beck.
However...
these guys will never make a major debut.
It's unfortunate,
but anyone who crosses me
will be destroyed!
Ran-san...
Eiji, in this world,
only the strongest survive.
In this world, power is everything.
And Ran-san has it.
And someone powerless like me,
just has to be smart and get around it.
That's the reality.
But Ryusuke, I'll become successful
no matter what I have to do.
Ah...On the sixteenth?
I can't. I got a red flag.
Come on, Maho. My father's friend
opened an Italian restaurant.
You know, in nighttime,
the view from there is so great.
All right, I'll think about it.
Oh, I gotta go to bathroom.
What kind of band is Beck?
They put their live [performance]
Before anything else.
Well, I just met the singer.
And?
He was just a tiny tot.
Yes, hello?
Oh, I dialed the wrong number.
Oh, it's Koyuki-kun?
Uh...Yes.
Maho is taking a shower
and can't come to the phone.
Anything you want me to tell her?
Oh?
About Monday's party.
Oh, the party...
Come to the party dressed
like you were invited to a ball.
And don't forget the present for the guest.
And who...
Hey, what're you laughing about?
You're kind, Koyuki.
But you don't seem to like my friends.
It's Christine's birthday party.
I wondered if you could come.
Hey you! This place is reserved today.
Don't mess around here...please.
Err...no...My friend is enjoy party.
Ah! Yoshito-kun!
Sorry, but plans were changed.
Now this party is only for school friends.
That's...
So others can't come in. Sorry.
Oh...
Please give this to Christine then.
Sure.
See ya!
Why?!
'Cause he really took it serious.
He looked so stupid.
Koyuki...
Hey! He don't give a fuck!
The Telecaster is gone.
Takano-san said to wait in the back.
Hey!
Hey! Wait!
Takano-san wants...
Hey!
T-Thief!
Huh?
Takano...
Crush!
Katahira-san, how is that Telecaster?
I made lots of adjustments.
Katahira...
Ohh...It's nice. I wanna buy it.
Huh? It's Tatsuya Katahira
of Loud Crime City.
Can't do that. This kid's gonna buy it.
I'll pay you double.
-I didn't reserve it...
-No, Taira asked me.
Oh...
I'm a drummer, but I've gotta be nice
and give guitars a chance, too.
If that kid doesn't buy it, let me know.
Is Loud really going to disband
after their next live performance?
Yup. You gotta know when to call it quits.
Come watch us.
Kid, the deadline is
the end of the month. Got it?
Yes!
Hmm...Katahira of Loud?
Yup...
It's true that Loud
is Japan's top rock band.
Let's go see them at the Budokan.
Stupid! It was sold out ages ago.
Hah! So different from us.
Loud wasn't popular from the start.
Let's just concentrate on today's show.
Right! Live performances are important.
But our problem right now is...
This!
We ordered 300 copies
and we have 210 left.
That's 42 copies each!
Friends, family, anyone you
can think of! Sell them all!
B-But I don't know 40 people!
If we don't get rid of these,
we'll end up with a huge debt!
-Oh...
Yo! We're Beck!
It's packed tonight,
but there's not much noise.
They're all waiting for the next band.
We should pump them up.
One, two...
Uh!
Yeah!
You open up the door
with negative aura
You say future is murky indeed...
I'm sick of hearing gripe.
Open up the door with negative aura
If you never change
It's probably the last time
I'll use this in a live performance.
I think there is no way
my life fizzle out
Thank you for all this time...
White Falcon.
You open up the door with negative aura
(I'm fed up fed up fed up)
When Loud disbands,
Japanese rock will die.
You say future is murky...
And that's not an understatement.
It's fact that Loud has carried
the Japanese scene on its shoulders.
Really?
And there's been no band
that can compare to Loud.
Our gas ran out.
Huh?
We can't run anymore.
You must know...
In the music scene,
something's always evolving.
Somewhere right now, there's an
unknown band making great music.
Is there such a band?
No one knows about them yet,
but they'll come onto the next music scene
and let us listen to the real McCoy.
See ya!
Katahira-san!
Don't chain down your affection
Awaken primal feeling
Don't benumb emotion
Sing out primal scream
Let loose every feeling
from joy to grief
Don't chain down your affection
Awaken primal feeling
Don't benumb emotion
Sing out primal scream
Let loose every feeling
from joy to grief
Don't chain down your affection
Awaken primal feeling
Don't benumb emotion
Sing out primal scream
Let loose every feeling
from joy to grief
He's gotten pretty good...that kid.
Let loose every feeling
from joy to grief
Go against headwind
or ride on the tailwind.
Game is in your hands.
How do you play?
Follow your brainstorm!
Could I get the CD?
Uh, yes. The band's called Beck.
Yes, a good band.
Especially guitar.
Yes!
The president of an
Indies label in Chicago?
Yup! It seems he just walked in by chance.
Well, there are lots
of foreigners around here.
Hmm...
Sun Factory Record...Frank Albin.
Never heard of it.
-Is it all right?
-He seemed nice.
All right. Cheers!
Another minute
Feelin' so fine
You turn the freeze
into warm light
Had a premonition
I've been waitin' ever since
My world comin' down
It's got me spinnin' 'round
If you really wanna fly
you gotta let go
Simply the most
big sensation
(once you're here you won't go back)
She's really pretty
One-eyed vision
(lose the fear it don't come back)
Little sister showed me
Really took me for a ride
My world comin' down
(once you're here you won't go back)
(lose the fear it don't come back)
I bought bags for the dog's poo.
"Live 17 'Three Days'"
Why do I hafta walk Beck?! Ryusuke!